{
  "introduction": null,
  "language_2": "en",
  "name": "1000_mots",
  "language_1": "fr",
  "voice_1": null,
  "pul_elements": [
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "comme",
      "answer": "as"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "je",
      "answer": "I"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "son",
      "answer": "his"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "que",
      "answer": "that"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "il",
      "answer": "he"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "était",
      "answer": "was"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pour",
      "answer": "for"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sur",
      "answer": "on"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sont",
      "answer": "are"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avec",
      "answer": "with"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ils",
      "answer": "they"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "être",
      "answer": "be"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "à",
      "answer": "at"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "un",
      "answer": "one"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avoir",
      "answer": "have"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ce",
      "answer": "this"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "à partir de",
      "answer": "from"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "par",
      "answer": "by"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaud",
      "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mot",
      "answer": "word"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mais",
      "answer": "but"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "que",
      "answer": "what"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "certains",
      "answer": "some"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "est",
      "answer": "is"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "il",
      "answer": "it"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vous",
      "answer": "you"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ou",
      "answer": "or"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "eu",
      "answer": "had"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "la",
      "answer": "the"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "de",
      "answer": "of"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "à",
      "answer": "to"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "et",
      "answer": "and"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "un",
      "answer": "a"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dans",
      "answer": "in"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nous",
      "answer": "we"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "boîte",
      "answer": "can"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dehors",
      "answer": "out"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "autre",
      "answer": "other"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étaient",
      "answer": "were"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "qui",
      "answer": "which"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "faire",
      "answer": "do"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "leur",
      "answer": "their"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "temps",
      "answer": "time"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "si",
      "answer": "if"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "volonté",
      "answer": "will"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "comment",
      "answer": "how"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dit",
      "answer": "said"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "un",
      "answer": "an"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaque",
      "answer": "each"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dire",
      "answer": "tell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ensemble",
      "answer": "set"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "trois",
      "answer": "three"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vouloir",
      "answer": "want"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "air",
      "answer": "air"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bien",
      "answer": "well"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aussi",
      "answer": "also"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jouer",
      "answer": "play"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "petit",
      "answer": "small"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fin",
      "answer": "end"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mettre",
      "answer": "put"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "maison",
      "answer": "home"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lire",
      "answer": "read"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "main",
      "answer": "hand"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "port",
      "answer": "port"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "grand",
      "answer": "large"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "épeler",
      "answer": "spell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ajouter",
      "answer": "add"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "même",
      "answer": "even"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "terre",
      "answer": "land"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ici",
      "answer": "here"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "il faut",
      "answer": "must"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "grand",
      "answer": "big"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "haut",
      "answer": "high"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tel",
      "answer": "such"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "suivre",
      "answer": "follow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "acte",
      "answer": "act"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pourquoi",
      "answer": "why"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "interroger",
      "answer": "ask"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "hommes",
      "answer": "men"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "changement",
      "answer": "change"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "est allé",
      "answer": "went"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lumière",
      "answer": "light"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "genre",
      "answer": "kind"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "de",
      "answer": "off"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "besoin",
      "answer": "need"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "maison",
      "answer": "house"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "image",
      "answer": "picture"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "essayer",
      "answer": "try"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nous",
      "answer": "us"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "encore",
      "answer": "again"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "animal",
      "answer": "animal"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "point",
      "answer": "point"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mère",
      "answer": "mother"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "monde",
      "answer": "world"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "près de",
      "answer": "near"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "construire",
      "answer": "build"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soi",
      "answer": "self"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "terre",
      "answer": "earth"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "père",
      "answer": "father"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tout",
      "answer": "any"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nouveau",
      "answer": "new"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "travail",
      "answer": "work"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "partie",
      "answer": "part"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "prendre",
      "answer": "take"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "obtenir",
      "answer": "get"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lieu",
      "answer": "place"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fabriqué",
      "answer": "made"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vivre",
      "answer": "live"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "où",
      "answer": "where"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "après",
      "answer": "after"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "arrière",
      "answer": "back"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peu",
      "answer": "little"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "seulement",
      "answer": "only"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tour",
      "answer": "round"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "homme",
      "answer": "man"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "année",
      "answer": "year"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "est venu",
      "answer": "came"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "montrer",
      "answer": "show"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tous",
      "answer": "every"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bon",
      "answer": "good"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moi",
      "answer": "me"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "donner",
      "answer": "give"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "notre",
      "answer": "our"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sous",
      "answer": "under"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nom",
      "answer": "name"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "très",
      "answer": "very"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "par",
      "answer": "through"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "juste",
      "answer": "just"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "forme",
      "answer": "form"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "phrase",
      "answer": "sentence"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "grand",
      "answer": "great"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "penser",
      "answer": "think"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dire",
      "answer": "say"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aider",
      "answer": "help"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "faible",
      "answer": "low"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ligne",
      "answer": "line"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "différer",
      "answer": "differ"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tour",
      "answer": "turn"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "la cause",
      "answer": "cause"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "beaucoup",
      "answer": "much"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "signifier",
      "answer": "mean"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avant",
      "answer": "before"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "déménagement",
      "answer": "move"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "droit",
      "answer": "right"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "garçon",
      "answer": "boy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vieux",
      "answer": "old"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "trop",
      "answer": "too"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "même",
      "answer": "same"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "elle",
      "answer": "she"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tous",
      "answer": "all"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "là",
      "answer": "there"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "quand",
      "answer": "when"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jusqu’à",
      "answer": "up"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "utiliser",
      "answer": "use"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "votre",
      "answer": "your"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "manière",
      "answer": "way"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sur",
      "answer": "about"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "beaucoup",
      "answer": "many"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "puis",
      "answer": "then"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "les",
      "answer": "them"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "écrire",
      "answer": "write"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voudrais",
      "answer": "would"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "comme",
      "answer": "like"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "si",
      "answer": "so"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ces",
      "answer": "these"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "son",
      "answer": "her"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "long",
      "answer": "long"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "faire",
      "answer": "make"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chose",
      "answer": "thing"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voir",
      "answer": "see"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lui",
      "answer": "him"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "deux",
      "answer": "two"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "a",
      "answer": "has"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "regarder",
      "answer": "look"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plus",
      "answer": "more"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jour",
      "answer": "day"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pourrait",
      "answer": "could"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aller",
      "answer": "go"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "venir",
      "answer": "come"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fait",
      "answer": "did"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nombre",
      "answer": "number"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "son",
      "answer": "sound"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aucun",
      "answer": "no"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plus",
      "answer": "most"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "personnes",
      "answer": "people"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ma",
      "answer": "my"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sur",
      "answer": "over"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "savoir",
      "answer": "know"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "eau",
      "answer": "water"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "que",
      "answer": "than"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "appel",
      "answer": "call"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "première",
      "answer": "first"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "qui",
      "answer": "who"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peut",
      "answer": "may"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vers le bas",
      "answer": "down"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "côté",
      "answer": "side"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "été",
      "answer": "been"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "maintenant",
      "answer": "now"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "trouver",
      "answer": "find"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tête",
      "answer": "head"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "supporter",
      "answer": "stand"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "propre",
      "answer": "own"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "page",
      "answer": "page"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "devrait",
      "answer": "should"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pays",
      "answer": "country"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "trouvé",
      "answer": "found"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "réponse",
      "answer": "answer"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "école",
      "answer": "school"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "croître",
      "answer": "grow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étude",
      "answer": "study"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "encore",
      "answer": "still"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "apprendre",
      "answer": "learn"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "usine",
      "answer": "plant"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "couvercle",
      "answer": "cover"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nourriture",
      "answer": "food"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soleil",
      "answer": "sun"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "quatre",
      "answer": "four"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entre",
      "answer": "between"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "état",
      "answer": "state"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "garder",
      "answer": "keep"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "œil",
      "answer": "eye"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jamais",
      "answer": "never"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dernier",
      "answer": "last"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "laisser",
      "answer": "let"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pensée",
      "answer": "thought"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ville",
      "answer": "city"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "arbre",
      "answer": "tree"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "traverser",
      "answer": "cross"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ferme",
      "answer": "farm"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dur",
      "answer": "hard"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "début",
      "answer": "start"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "puissance",
      "answer": "might"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "histoire",
      "answer": "story"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "scie",
      "answer": "saw"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "loin",
      "answer": "far"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mer",
      "answer": "sea"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tirer",
      "answer": "draw"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gauche",
      "answer": "left"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tard",
      "answer": "late"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "courir",
      "answer": "run"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "needs a context",
      "answer": "don’t"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tandis que",
      "answer": "while"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "presse",
      "answer": "press"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "proche",
      "answer": "close"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nuit",
      "answer": "night"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "réel",
      "answer": "real"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vie",
      "answer": "life"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peu",
      "answer": "few"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nord",
      "answer": "north"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "livre",
      "answer": "book"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "porter",
      "answer": "carry"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "a pris",
      "answer": "took"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "science",
      "answer": "science"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "manger",
      "answer": "eat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chambre",
      "answer": "room"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ami",
      "answer": "friend"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "a commencé",
      "answer": "began"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "idée",
      "answer": "idea"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poisson",
      "answer": "fish"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "montagne",
      "answer": "mountain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "Arrêtez",
      "answer": "stop"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "une fois",
      "answer": "once"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "base",
      "answer": "base"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entendre",
      "answer": "hear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cheval",
      "answer": "horse"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coupe",
      "answer": "cut"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sûr",
      "answer": "sure"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "regarder",
      "answer": "watch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "couleur",
      "answer": "color"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "face",
      "answer": "face"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bois",
      "answer": "wood"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "principal",
      "answer": "main"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ouvert",
      "answer": "open"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "paraître",
      "answer": "seem"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ensemble",
      "answer": "together"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "suivant",
      "answer": "next"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "blanc",
      "answer": "white"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "enfants",
      "answer": "children"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "commencer",
      "answer": "begin"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "eu",
      "answer": "got"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "marcher",
      "answer": "walk"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "exemple",
      "answer": "example"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "facilité",
      "answer": "ease"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "papier",
      "answer": "paper"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "groupe",
      "answer": "group"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "toujours",
      "answer": "always"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "musique",
      "answer": "music"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ceux",
      "answer": "those"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tous les deux",
      "answer": "both"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "marque",
      "answer": "mark"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "souvent",
      "answer": "often"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lettre",
      "answer": "letter"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jusqu’à ce que",
      "answer": "until"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mile",
      "answer": "mile"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rivière",
      "answer": "river"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voiture",
      "answer": "car"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pieds",
      "answer": "feet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soins",
      "answer": "care"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "deuxième",
      "answer": "second"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "assez",
      "answer": "enough"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plaine",
      "answer": "plain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fille",
      "answer": "girl"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "habituel",
      "answer": "usual"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jeune",
      "answer": "young"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "prêt",
      "answer": "ready"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "au-dessus",
      "answer": "above"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jamais",
      "answer": "ever"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rouge",
      "answer": "red"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "liste",
      "answer": "list"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bien que",
      "answer": "though"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sentir",
      "answer": "feel"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "parler",
      "answer": "talk"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "oiseau",
      "answer": "bird"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bientôt",
      "answer": "soon"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "corps",
      "answer": "body"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chien",
      "answer": "dog"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "famille",
      "answer": "family"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "direct",
      "answer": "direct"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pose",
      "answer": "pose"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "laisser",
      "answer": "leave"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chanson",
      "answer": "song"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mesurer",
      "answer": "measure"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "porte",
      "answer": "door"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "produit",
      "answer": "product"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "noir",
      "answer": "black"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "court",
      "answer": "short"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chiffre",
      "answer": "numeral"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "classe",
      "answer": "class"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vent",
      "answer": "wind"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "question",
      "answer": "question"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "arriver",
      "answer": "happen"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "complète",
      "answer": "complete"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "navire",
      "answer": "ship"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "zone",
      "answer": "area"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moitié",
      "answer": "half"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rock",
      "answer": "rock"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ordre",
      "answer": "order"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "feu",
      "answer": "fire"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sud",
      "answer": "south"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "problème",
      "answer": "problem"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pièce",
      "answer": "piece"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dit",
      "answer": "told"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "savait",
      "answer": "knew"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "passer",
      "answer": "pass"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "depuis",
      "answer": "since"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "haut",
      "answer": "top"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ensemble",
      "answer": "whole"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "roi",
      "answer": "king"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rue",
      "answer": "street"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pouce",
      "answer": "inch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "multiplier",
      "answer": "multiply"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rien",
      "answer": "nothing"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cours",
      "answer": "course"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rester",
      "answer": "stay"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "roue",
      "answer": "wheel"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plein",
      "answer": "full"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "force",
      "answer": "force"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bleu",
      "answer": "blue"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "objet",
      "answer": "object"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "décider",
      "answer": "decide"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "surface",
      "answer": "surface"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "profond",
      "answer": "deep"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lune",
      "answer": "moon"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "île",
      "answer": "island"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pied",
      "answer": "foot"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "système",
      "answer": "system"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "occupé",
      "answer": "busy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "test",
      "answer": "test"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "record",
      "answer": "record"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bateau",
      "answer": "boat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "commun",
      "answer": "common"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "or",
      "answer": "gold"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "possible",
      "answer": "possible"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plan",
      "answer": "plane"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "place",
      "answer": "stead"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sec",
      "answer": "dry"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "se demander",
      "answer": "wonder"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rire",
      "answer": "laugh"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mille",
      "answer": "thousand"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "il ya",
      "answer": "ago"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ran",
      "answer": "ran"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vérifier",
      "answer": "check"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jeu",
      "answer": "game"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "forme",
      "answer": "shape"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "assimiler",
      "answer": "equate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaud",
      "answer": "hot"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "manquer",
      "answer": "miss"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "apporté",
      "answer": "brought"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaleur",
      "answer": "heat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "neige",
      "answer": "snow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pneu",
      "answer": "tire"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "apporter",
      "answer": "bring"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "oui",
      "answer": "yes"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lointain",
      "answer": "distant"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "remplir",
      "answer": "fill"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "est",
      "answer": "east"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peindre",
      "answer": "paint"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "langue",
      "answer": "language"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entre",
      "answer": "among"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "unité",
      "answer": "unit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "puissance",
      "answer": "power"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ville",
      "answer": "town"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fin",
      "answer": "fine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "certain",
      "answer": "certain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voler",
      "answer": "fly"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tomber",
      "answer": "fall"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "conduire",
      "answer": "lead"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cri",
      "answer": "cry"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sombre",
      "answer": "dark"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "machine",
      "answer": "machine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "Note",
      "answer": "note"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "patienter",
      "answer": "wait"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plan",
      "answer": "plan"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "figure",
      "answer": "figure"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étoile",
      "answer": "star"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "boîte",
      "answer": "box"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nom",
      "answer": "noun"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "domaine",
      "answer": "field"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "reste",
      "answer": "rest"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "correct",
      "answer": "correct"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "capable",
      "answer": "able"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "livre",
      "answer": "pound"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "Terminé",
      "answer": "done"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "beauté",
      "answer": "beauty"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entraînement",
      "answer": "drive"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "résisté",
      "answer": "stood"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "contenir",
      "answer": "contain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avant",
      "answer": "front"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "enseigner",
      "answer": "teach"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "semaine",
      "answer": "week"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "finale",
      "answer": "final"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "donné",
      "answer": "gave"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vert",
      "answer": "green"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "oh",
      "answer": "oh"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rapide",
      "answer": "quick"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "développer",
      "answer": "develop"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "océan",
      "answer": "ocean"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaud",
      "answer": "warm"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gratuit",
      "answer": "free"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "minute",
      "answer": "minute"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fort",
      "answer": "strong"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "spécial",
      "answer": "special"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "esprit",
      "answer": "mind"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "derrière",
      "answer": "behind"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "clair",
      "answer": "clear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "queue",
      "answer": "tail"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "produire",
      "answer": "produce"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fait",
      "answer": "fact"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "espace",
      "answer": "space"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entendu",
      "answer": "heard"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "meilleur",
      "answer": "best"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "heure",
      "answer": "hour"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mieux",
      "answer": "better"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "VRAI",
      "answer": "true"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pendant",
      "answer": "during"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cent",
      "answer": "hundred"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cinq",
      "answer": "five"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rappeler",
      "answer": "remember"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étape",
      "answer": "step"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tôt",
      "answer": "early"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tenir",
      "answer": "hold"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ouest",
      "answer": "west"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sol",
      "answer": "ground"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "intérêt",
      "answer": "interest"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "atteindre",
      "answer": "reach"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rapide",
      "answer": "fast"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "verbe",
      "answer": "verb"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chanter",
      "answer": "sing"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "écouter",
      "answer": "listen"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "six",
      "answer": "six"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "table",
      "answer": "table"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "Voyage",
      "answer": "travel"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moins",
      "answer": "less"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "matin",
      "answer": "morning"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dix",
      "answer": "ten"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "simple",
      "answer": "simple"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plusieurs",
      "answer": "several"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voyelle",
      "answer": "vowel"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vers",
      "answer": "toward"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "guerre",
      "answer": "war"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poser",
      "answer": "lay"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "contre",
      "answer": "against"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "modèle",
      "answer": "pattern"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lent",
      "answer": "slow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "centre",
      "answer": "center"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "amour",
      "answer": "love"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "personne",
      "answer": "person"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "argent",
      "answer": "money"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "servir",
      "answer": "serve"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "apparaître",
      "answer": "appear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "route",
      "answer": "road"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "carte",
      "answer": "map"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pluie",
      "answer": "rain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "règle",
      "answer": "rule"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gouverner",
      "answer": "govern"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tirer",
      "answer": "pull"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "froid",
      "answer": "cold"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avis",
      "answer": "notice"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voix",
      "answer": "voice"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "énergie",
      "answer": "energy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chasse",
      "answer": "hunt"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "probable",
      "answer": "probable"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lit",
      "answer": "bed"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "frère",
      "answer": "brother"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "œuf",
      "answer": "egg"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tour",
      "answer": "ride"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cellule",
      "answer": "cell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "croire",
      "answer": "believe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peut-être",
      "answer": "perhaps"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "choisir",
      "answer": "pick"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soudain",
      "answer": "sudden"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "compter",
      "answer": "count"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "carré",
      "answer": "square"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "raison",
      "answer": "reason"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "longueur",
      "answer": "length"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "représenter",
      "answer": "represent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "art",
      "answer": "art"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sujet",
      "answer": "subject"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "région",
      "answer": "region"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "taille",
      "answer": "size"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "varier",
      "answer": "vary"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "régler",
      "answer": "settle"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "parler",
      "answer": "speak"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poids",
      "answer": "weight"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "général",
      "answer": "general"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "glace",
      "answer": "ice"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "question",
      "answer": "matter"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cercle",
      "answer": "circle"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "paire",
      "answer": "pair"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "inclure",
      "answer": "include"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fracture",
      "answer": "divide"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "syllabe",
      "answer": "syllable"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "feutre",
      "answer": "felt"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "grandiose",
      "answer": "grand"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "balle",
      "answer": "ball"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "encore",
      "answer": "yet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vague",
      "answer": "wave"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tomber",
      "answer": "drop"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cœur",
      "answer": "heart"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "h",
      "answer": "am"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "présent",
      "answer": "present"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lourd",
      "answer": "heavy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "danse",
      "answer": "dance"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moteur",
      "answer": "engine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "position",
      "answer": "position"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bras",
      "answer": "arm"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "large",
      "answer": "wide"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voile",
      "answer": "sail"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "matériel",
      "answer": "material"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fraction",
      "answer": "fraction"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "forêt",
      "answer": "forest"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "s’asseoir",
      "answer": "sit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "course",
      "answer": "race"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fenêtre",
      "answer": "window"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "magasin",
      "answer": "store"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "été",
      "answer": "summer"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "train",
      "answer": "train"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sommeil",
      "answer": "sleep"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "prouver",
      "answer": "prove"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "seul",
      "answer": "lone"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jambe",
      "answer": "leg"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "exercice",
      "answer": "exercise"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mur",
      "answer": "wall"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "capture",
      "answer": "catch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "monture",
      "answer": "mount"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "souhaiter",
      "answer": "wish"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ciel",
      "answer": "sky"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "conseil",
      "answer": "board"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "joie",
      "answer": "joy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "hiver",
      "answer": "winter"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sat",
      "answer": "sat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "écrit",
      "answer": "written"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sauvage",
      "answer": "wild"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "instrument",
      "answer": "instrument"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "conservé",
      "answer": "kept"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "verre",
      "answer": "glass"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "herbe",
      "answer": "grass"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vache",
      "answer": "cow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "emploi",
      "answer": "job"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bord",
      "answer": "edge"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "signe",
      "answer": "sign"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "visite",
      "answer": "visit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "passé",
      "answer": "past"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "doux",
      "answer": "soft"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "amusement",
      "answer": "fun"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "clair",
      "answer": "bright"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gaz",
      "answer": "gas"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "temps",
      "answer": "weather"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mois",
      "answer": "month"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "million",
      "answer": "million"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "porter",
      "answer": "bear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "finition",
      "answer": "finish"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "heureux",
      "answer": "happy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "espoir",
      "answer": "hope"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fleur",
      "answer": "flower"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vêtir",
      "answer": "clothe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étrange",
      "answer": "strange"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "disparu",
      "answer": "gone"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "commerce",
      "answer": "trade"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mélodie",
      "answer": "melody"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voyage",
      "answer": "trip"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bureau",
      "answer": "office"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "recevoir",
      "answer": "receive"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rangée",
      "answer": "row"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bouche",
      "answer": "mouth"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "exact",
      "answer": "exact"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "symbole",
      "answer": "symbol"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mourir",
      "answer": "die"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moins",
      "answer": "least"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "difficulté",
      "answer": "trouble"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cri",
      "answer": "shout"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sauf",
      "answer": "except"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "écrit",
      "answer": "wrote"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "semence",
      "answer": "seed"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ton",
      "answer": "tone"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "joindre",
      "answer": "join"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "suggérer",
      "answer": "suggest"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "propre",
      "answer": "clean"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pause",
      "answer": "break"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dame",
      "answer": "lady"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cour",
      "answer": "yard"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "augmenter",
      "answer": "rise"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mauvais",
      "answer": "bad"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coup",
      "answer": "blow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "huile",
      "answer": "oil"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sang",
      "answer": "blood"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "toucher",
      "answer": "touch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "a augmenté",
      "answer": "grew"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cent",
      "answer": "cent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mélanger",
      "answer": "mix"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "équipe",
      "answer": "team"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fil",
      "answer": "wire"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coût",
      "answer": "cost"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "perdu",
      "answer": "lost"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "brun",
      "answer": "brown"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "porter",
      "answer": "wear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jardin",
      "answer": "garden"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "égal",
      "answer": "equal"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "expédié",
      "answer": "sent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "choisir",
      "answer": "choose"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "est tombé",
      "answer": "fell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "s’adapter",
      "answer": "fit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "débit",
      "answer": "flow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "juste",
      "answer": "fair"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "banque",
      "answer": "bank"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "recueillir",
      "answer": "collect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sauver",
      "answer": "save"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "contrôle",
      "answer": "control"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "décimal",
      "answer": "decimal"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "oreille",
      "answer": "ear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "autre",
      "answer": "else"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tout à fait",
      "answer": "quite"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cassé",
      "answer": "broke"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cas",
      "answer": "case"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "milieu",
      "answer": "middle"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tuer",
      "answer": "kill"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fils",
      "answer": "son"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lac",
      "answer": "lake"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moment",
      "answer": "moment"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "échelle",
      "answer": "scale"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fort",
      "answer": "loud"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "printemps",
      "answer": "spring"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "observer",
      "answer": "observe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "enfant",
      "answer": "child"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "droit",
      "answer": "straight"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "consonne",
      "answer": "consonant"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nation",
      "answer": "nation"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dictionnaire",
      "answer": "dictionary"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lait",
      "answer": "milk"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vitesse",
      "answer": "speed"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "méthode",
      "answer": "method"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "organe",
      "answer": "organ"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "payer",
      "answer": "pay"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "âge",
      "answer": "age"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "section",
      "answer": "section"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "robe",
      "answer": "dress"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nuage",
      "answer": "cloud"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "surprise",
      "answer": "surprise"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "calme",
      "answer": "quiet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pierre",
      "answer": "stone"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "minuscule",
      "answer": "tiny"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "montée",
      "answer": "climb"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "frais",
      "answer": "cool"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "conception",
      "answer": "design"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pauvres",
      "answer": "poor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lot",
      "answer": "lot"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "expérience",
      "answer": "experiment"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bas",
      "answer": "bottom"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "clé",
      "answer": "key"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fer",
      "answer": "iron"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "unique",
      "answer": "single"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bâton",
      "answer": "stick"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plat",
      "answer": "flat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vingt",
      "answer": "twenty"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peau",
      "answer": "skin"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sourire",
      "answer": "smile"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pli",
      "answer": "crease"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "trou",
      "answer": "hole"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sauter",
      "answer": "jump"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bébé",
      "answer": "baby"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "huit",
      "answer": "eight"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "village",
      "answer": "village"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "se rencontrent",
      "answer": "meet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "racine",
      "answer": "root"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "acheter",
      "answer": "buy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "augmenter",
      "answer": "raise"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "résoudre",
      "answer": "solve"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "métal",
      "answer": "metal"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "si",
      "answer": "whether"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pousser",
      "answer": "push"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sept",
      "answer": "seven"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "paragraphe",
      "answer": "paragraph"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "troisième",
      "answer": "third"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "doit",
      "answer": "shall"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "en attente",
      "answer": "held"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cheveux",
      "answer": "hair"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "décrire",
      "answer": "describe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cuisinier",
      "answer": "cook"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étage",
      "answer": "floor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaque",
      "answer": "either"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "résultat",
      "answer": "result"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "brûler",
      "answer": "burn"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "colline",
      "answer": "hill"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coffre-fort",
      "answer": "safe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chat",
      "answer": "cat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "siècle",
      "answer": "century"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "envisager",
      "answer": "consider"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "type",
      "answer": "type"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "droit",
      "answer": "law"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peu",
      "answer": "bit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "côte",
      "answer": "coast"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "copie",
      "answer": "copy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "phrase",
      "answer": "phrase"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "silencieux",
      "answer": "silent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "haut",
      "answer": "tall"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sable",
      "answer": "sand"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sol",
      "answer": "soil"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rouleau",
      "answer": "roll"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "température",
      "answer": "temperature"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "doigt",
      "answer": "finger"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "industrie",
      "answer": "industry"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "valeur",
      "answer": "value"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lutte",
      "answer": "fight"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mensonge",
      "answer": "lie"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "battre",
      "answer": "beat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "exciter",
      "answer": "excite"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "naturel",
      "answer": "natural"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vue",
      "answer": "view"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sens",
      "answer": "sense"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "capital",
      "answer": "capital"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ne sera pas",
      "answer": "won’t"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaise",
      "answer": "chair"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "danger",
      "answer": "danger"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fruit",
      "answer": "fruit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "riche",
      "answer": "rich"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "épais",
      "answer": "thick"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soldat",
      "answer": "soldier"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "processus",
      "answer": "process"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fonctionner",
      "answer": "operate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pratique",
      "answer": "practice"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "séparé",
      "answer": "separate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "difficile",
      "answer": "difficult"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "médecin",
      "answer": "doctor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "s’il vous plaît",
      "answer": "please"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "protéger",
      "answer": "protect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "midi",
      "answer": "noon"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "récolte",
      "answer": "crop"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "moderne",
      "answer": "modern"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "élément",
      "answer": "element"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "frapper",
      "answer": "hit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "étudiant",
      "answer": "student"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coin",
      "answer": "corner"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "partie",
      "answer": "party"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "alimentation",
      "answer": "supply"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dont",
      "answer": "whose"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "localiser",
      "answer": "locate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "anneau",
      "answer": "ring"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "caractère",
      "answer": "character"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "insecte",
      "answer": "insect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pris",
      "answer": "caught"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "période",
      "answer": "period"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "indiquer",
      "answer": "indicate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "radio",
      "answer": "radio"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rayon",
      "answer": "spoke"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "atome",
      "answer": "atom"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "humain",
      "answer": "human"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "histoire",
      "answer": "history"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "effet",
      "answer": "effect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "électrique",
      "answer": "electric"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "attendre",
      "answer": "expect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "os",
      "answer": "bone"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rail",
      "answer": "rail"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "imaginer",
      "answer": "imagine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "fournir",
      "answer": "provide"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "se mettre d’accord",
      "answer": "agree"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ainsi",
      "answer": "thus"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "doux",
      "answer": "gentle"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "femme",
      "answer": "woman"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "capitaine",
      "answer": "captain"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "deviner",
      "answer": "guess"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nécessaire",
      "answer": "necessary"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "net",
      "answer": "sharp"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aile",
      "answer": "wing"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "créer",
      "answer": "create"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "voisin",
      "answer": "neighbor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lavage",
      "answer": "wash"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chauve-souris",
      "answer": "bat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "plutôt",
      "answer": "rather"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "foule",
      "answer": "crowd"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "blé",
      "answer": "corn"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "comparer",
      "answer": "compare"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poème",
      "answer": "poem"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaîne",
      "answer": "string"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cloche",
      "answer": "bell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dépendre",
      "answer": "depend"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "viande",
      "answer": "meat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rub",
      "answer": "rub"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tube",
      "answer": "tube"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "célèbre",
      "answer": "famous"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dollar",
      "answer": "dollar"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "courant",
      "answer": "stream"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peur",
      "answer": "fear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vue",
      "answer": "sight"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mince",
      "answer": "thin"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "triangle",
      "answer": "triangle"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "planète",
      "answer": "planet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "se dépêcher",
      "answer": "hurry"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chef",
      "answer": "chief"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "colonie",
      "answer": "colony"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "horloge",
      "answer": "clock"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mine",
      "answer": "mine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "lien",
      "answer": "tie"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entrer",
      "answer": "enter"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "majeur",
      "answer": "major"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "frais",
      "answer": "fresh"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "recherche",
      "answer": "search"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "envoyer",
      "answer": "send"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jaune",
      "answer": "yellow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pistolet",
      "answer": "gun"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "permettre",
      "answer": "allow"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "impression",
      "answer": "print"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mort",
      "answer": "dead"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "place",
      "answer": "spot"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "désert",
      "answer": "desert"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "costume",
      "answer": "suit"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "courant",
      "answer": "current"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ascenseur",
      "answer": "lift"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rose",
      "answer": "rose"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "arriver",
      "answer": "arrive"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "maître",
      "answer": "master"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "piste",
      "answer": "track"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mère",
      "answer": "parent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rivage",
      "answer": "shore"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "division",
      "answer": "division"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "feuille",
      "answer": "sheet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "substance",
      "answer": "substance"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "favoriser",
      "answer": "favor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "relier",
      "answer": "connect"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poste",
      "answer": "post"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "passer",
      "answer": "spend"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "corde",
      "answer": "chord"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "graisse",
      "answer": "fat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "heureux",
      "answer": "glad"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "original",
      "answer": "original"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "part",
      "answer": "share"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "station",
      "answer": "station"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "papa",
      "answer": "dad"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pain",
      "answer": "bread"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "charger",
      "answer": "charge"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "propre",
      "answer": "proper"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bar",
      "answer": "bar"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "proposition",
      "answer": "offer"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "segment",
      "answer": "segment"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "esclave",
      "answer": "slave"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "canard",
      "answer": "duck"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "instant",
      "answer": "instant"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "marché",
      "answer": "market"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "degré",
      "answer": "degree"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peupler",
      "answer": "populate"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "poussin",
      "answer": "chick"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cher",
      "answer": "dear"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ennemi",
      "answer": "enemy"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "répondre",
      "answer": "reply"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "boisson",
      "answer": "drink"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "se produire",
      "answer": "occur"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "support",
      "answer": "support"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "discours",
      "answer": "speech"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nature",
      "answer": "nature"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gamme",
      "answer": "range"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vapeur",
      "answer": "steam"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mouvement",
      "answer": "motion"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chemin",
      "answer": "path"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "liquide",
      "answer": "liquid"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "enregistrer",
      "answer": "log"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "signifiait",
      "answer": "meant"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "quotient",
      "answer": "quotient"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "dents",
      "answer": "teeth"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coquille",
      "answer": "shell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "cou",
      "answer": "neck"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "oxygène",
      "answer": "oxygen"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sucre",
      "answer": "sugar"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "décès",
      "answer": "death"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "assez",
      "answer": "pretty"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "compétence",
      "answer": "skill"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "femmes",
      "answer": "women"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "saison",
      "answer": "season"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "solution",
      "answer": "solution"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "aimant",
      "answer": "magnet"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "argent",
      "answer": "silver"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "merci",
      "answer": "thank"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "branche",
      "answer": "branch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rencontre",
      "answer": "match"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "suffixe",
      "answer": "suffix"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "particulièrement",
      "answer": "especially"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "figue",
      "answer": "fig"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "peur",
      "answer": "afraid"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "énorme",
      "answer": "huge"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sœur",
      "answer": "sister"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "acier",
      "answer": "steel"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "discuter",
      "answer": "discuss"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "avant",
      "answer": "forward"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "similaire",
      "answer": "similar"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "guider",
      "answer": "guide"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "expérience",
      "answer": "experience"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "score",
      "answer": "score"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pomme",
      "answer": "apple"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "acheté",
      "answer": "bought"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "LED",
      "answer": "led"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pas",
      "answer": "pitch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "manteau",
      "answer": "coat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "masse",
      "answer": "mass"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "carte",
      "answer": "card"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bande",
      "answer": "band"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "corde",
      "answer": "rope"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "glissement",
      "answer": "slip"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gagner",
      "answer": "win"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "rêver",
      "answer": "dream"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soirée",
      "answer": "evening"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "condition",
      "answer": "condition"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "alimentation",
      "answer": "feed"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "outil",
      "answer": "tool"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "total",
      "answer": "total"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "de base",
      "answer": "basic"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "odeur",
      "answer": "smell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vallée",
      "answer": "valley"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "ni",
      "answer": "nor"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "double",
      "answer": "double"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "siège",
      "answer": "seat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "continuer",
      "answer": "continue"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bloc",
      "answer": "block"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "graphique",
      "answer": "chart"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chapeau",
      "answer": "hat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "vendre",
      "answer": "sell"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "succès",
      "answer": "success"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "entreprise",
      "answer": "company"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "soustraire",
      "answer": "subtract"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "événement",
      "answer": "event"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "particulier",
      "answer": "particular"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "accord",
      "answer": "deal"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "baignade",
      "answer": "swim"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "terme",
      "answer": "term"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "opposé",
      "answer": "opposite"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "femme",
      "answer": "wife"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chaussure",
      "answer": "shoe"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "épaule",
      "answer": "shoulder"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "propagation",
      "answer": "spread"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "organiser",
      "answer": "arrange"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "camp",
      "answer": "camp"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "inventer",
      "answer": "invent"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "coton",
      "answer": "cotton"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "né",
      "answer": "born"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "déterminer",
      "answer": "determine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "litre",
      "answer": "quart"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "neuf",
      "answer": "nine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "camion",
      "answer": "truck"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "bruit",
      "answer": "noise"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "niveau",
      "answer": "level"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "chance",
      "answer": "chance"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "recueillir",
      "answer": "gather"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "boutique",
      "answer": "shop"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "tronçon",
      "answer": "stretch"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "jeter",
      "answer": "throw"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "éclat",
      "answer": "shine"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "propriété",
      "answer": "property"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "colonne",
      "answer": "column"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "molécule",
      "answer": "molecule"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sélectionner",
      "answer": "select"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "mal",
      "answer": "wrong"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "gris",
      "answer": "gray"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "répétition",
      "answer": "repeat"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "exiger",
      "answer": "require"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "large",
      "answer": "broad"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "préparer",
      "answer": "prepare"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "sel",
      "answer": "salt"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "nez",
      "answer": "nose"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "pluriel",
      "answer": "plural"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "colère",
      "answer": "anger"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "revendication",
      "answer": "claim"
    },
    {
      "details": [
        {
          "description": ""
        }
      ],
      "question": "continent",
      "answer": "continent"
    }
  ],
  "subject": "learn_english_1000_words",
  "type": "BUTTON",
  "sentence": null,
  "voice_2": null,
  "number": "1"
}
